makeupera.com 2017-06-06

# PRIVACY POLICY - MakeupEra

This privacy policy is aimed to set out as to how Makeupera uses and protects the information that you give Makeupera when you use this website.

  Makeupera is committed to ensure that your privacy is always protected. While using this site if at any stage you are asked to provide any information for your identification, it is to be understood that it is being done so in accordance with the privacy statement.

  Makeupera may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. No prior notification will be given. You should check this page time and again to ensure that you are happy with the changes and are aware of them. This policy is effective from 2014.

### KIND OF INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT

We may collect the following information:

  1.)name and job title

  2.)Location and address

  3.)contact information including email address

  4.)preferences and interests

  5.)other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers 

### What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  1.)Internal record keeping.

  2.)We may use the information to improve our products and services.

  3.)We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.

  5.)From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### YOUR ACCEPTANCE TO THE TERMS

By using this site, you show interest in accepting to the policy. 

### CONTACTING US

For any questions or queries about this Privacy Policy, or about the practices of the site, please feel free to contact us at: [http://www.makeupera.com](http://www.makeupera.com/).

_________________________________________________________________
